M. Sanjay kumar

Structural / Architecture draughtsman.

Al dhani building, Al asakir st., Najma, Doha , qatar +974 66461704 | sanjaykumarsrt10@gmail.com



Objectives

A result oriented professional with over 3 years of working experience in structural / Architecture draughtsman. Seeking a challenging perception in the field of Structural draughtsman, where I can gain valuable experience can contribute towards the success of the organization through utilization of my knowledge and experience. Capable of achieving timely project completion.

Technical Skills

- Ms Excel
- AutoCAD
- Revit architecture &structures
- Staad pro

Keyskills

- Hands on training with Architectural, Civil and Structural drafting.
- Revit Architectural in modeling and 3D Designing.
- Physical and 3D Modeling, Rendering Material, Lights and Camera.
- Computer aided drafting with conventional method of graphic communication to solve and basic design related problems.
- Time management skills to prioritize projects and the ability to multi-task.
- Attention to Detail being careful about detail and thorough in completing work tasks.

Work Experience

Shaam . Design engineer & consultant - Ras al khamiah (UAE)

Structural / Architecture draughtsman May 2016 - June 2018

Responsibilities

- Prepare detailed drawings of architectural designs and plans for buildings and structures according to specifications provided by architect.
- Preparation of Revit & 3ds max designing with interiors & exteriors work.
- Conceptualizing and developing plan & all over the design of project.
- Preparation of interiors drawings, working drawing site visits etc.
- To draw different views of interiors 3d images.
- To draw Revit designing software with 3d hall, bed & kitchen perspectives

Shakti modern builders, engineering & contracts

Autocad draftsman July 2018 - jan 2019

Responsibilities

- I have good knowledge's of RCC, Brick, Tiles, Electric plumbing work etc.
- Good relation with client, contractor's, labors etc.
- To complete of four storeys building for completion of my civil Forman construction company in two years.
- I have good knowledge's of center line plan, columns, beam position, checking of slab and beam, steel binding, centering and shuttering work.
- Mixing the ratio of sand, cement, & aggregate for RCC footing, columns, slab brick works, plasters of ratio completely knowledge of construction work.
- Provided quality AutoCAD service in line with department drafting standards.
- Knowledge of materials, methods, and the tools involved in the construction or repair of houses, buildings, or other structures such as highways and roads.

Education

B.E Civil engineering (2016),

University of engineering - BIT campus, Anna university.

Personal strengths

- Honesty
- Positive attitude
- Problem solving ability
- Quick learner
- I never give up

Personal info

Date of birth : Jan 15,1995

Martial status. : Single

Language known. : Tamil & English

Nationality. : Indian

Permanent Address : 22/103A, cauvery nagar,

Kulithalai, karur(dt.),

Tamilnadu, India.

Postal code - 639104.

Passport & visa status

Passport holder. - Indian
Passport number - S5240707

Visa type - Resident permit

Visa validity - 2019 - 2021

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Date:

Place: Doha